<data>

	<event start="May 20 1979" title="Konjo School is Founded">
	The Sacramento-based Konjo School of Martial Arts is founded in 1979 by David Butler.  
	Patterned after the traditional martial arts schools of Japan, the Konjo School of Martial Arts (which translates 
	"place where one learns perseverance") was dedicated to the traditional budo arts of bujitsu which included 
	karate, judo, and weapons.  Konjo blends the principles of dedication, hard training, 
	and technical excellence with a culture of unity, family and mutual support.
    </event>
    
    <event start="Sep 20 1979" end="July 31 1987" isDuration="true" title="South Sacramento">
    The Konjo School of Martial Arts is started in a garage with seven students.  In less than a year it moves 
    to a large church building in South Sacramento, quickly growing to more than 70 students.
	</event>
	
	<event start="June 1 1984" title="First Black Belts Promoted">
	The first group of Konjo black belts are promoted.  Among them are Lewis Mace, Jimmy Caruthers and Carl Grace.
    </event>
    
    <event start="June 1 1985" title="Konjo Challenge">
    The school begins a series of High Sierra summer camps called "Konjo Challenge."  These popular camps 
    bring together martial arts students and instructors from a variety of disciplines for three-day intensive 
    instruction and cross training seminars.
    </event>
    
    <event start="Aug 1 1986" end="July 1 1988" isDuration="true" title="Konjo - Roseville">
    Al Ikemoto joins the Konjo School of Martial Arts staff, beginning a long and successful instructional 
    partnership with Mr. Butler.  At this time a Roseville branch of the school is started at the 
    Roseville Community Center.
	</event>
    
	<event start="Feb 1 1987" end="May 31 1990" isDuration="true" title="Sacramento Training Facility">
	The school opens the Sacramento Martial Arts and Sports Center.  This facility remains open for two years 
	and marks the beginning of serious competitive judo and karate for the Konjo School of Martial 
	Arts.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Jan 1 1989" title="Team Sacramento Founded">
	While at the Sacramento Martial Arts and Sport Center, Mr. Butler founds Team Sacramento as the competitive 
	arm of the school.  The team's focus is on competitive judo and karate.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Jun 1 1990" end="Jun 1 2007" isDuration="true" title="JFK High School">
	The Konjo School of Martial Arts and Team Sacramento move to John F. Kennedy High School.  This allows 
	the club to minimize expenses and send students abroad to compete in local, state, national and international 
	events.  The club remains at JFK High School for 17 years.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Apr 1 1999" end="Mar 31 2006" isDuration="true" title="Ikemoto - Head Instructor">
	Al Ikemoto is appointed Head Instructor of the Konjo School of Martial Arts and Team Sacramento Judo.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Apr 1 2006" title="Goodall - Head Instructor">
	After 16 years as a competitor, and 12 years as an assistant instructor, Brent Goodall is appointed 
	Head Instructor of the Konjo School of Martial Arts and Team Sacramento Judo.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Sep 1 2006" title="Roseville Location Opens">
	Team Sacramento Judo opens a new location in Roseville.  Several new students 
	and families join; quick growth requires relocation to a larger facility.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Oct 7 2007" end="Mar 31 2011" isDuration="true" title="Ultimate Training Center">
	Thanks to UFC fighters James Irvin and Scott Smith, in October of 2007 Team Sacramento Judo relocates to the 
	newly-opened Ultimate Training Center in Roseville.  The state-of-the-art UTC facility features over 2000 
	square feet of mat space.  Several new students and families join the team.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Jun 1 2008" end="Nov 4 2008" isDuration="true" title="Ultimate Fitness">
	After nearly 18 years at JFK High School, and thanks to WEC World Champion Urijah Faber, Team Sacramento Judo 
	temporarily relocates it's Sacramento branch to Ultimate Fitness' state-of-the-art training facility in downtown Sacramento.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Nov 18 2008" end="Nov 16 2011" isDuration="true" title="Capital City BJJ">
	Team Sacramento Judo relocates it's Sacramento dojo to the Capital City Brazilian Jiu Jitsu facility.
	</event>
	
	<event start="May 2 2009" title="Folsom MMA">
	Team Sacramento Judo begins Saturday classes at Folsom Mixed Martial Arts.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Oct 31 2011" title="Junior World Team Qualifier">
	Syria Rhodes becomes the first Team Sacramento Judo competitor to qualify for the US Junior World Team and 
	competes at the 2011 Junior World Championships in Capetown, South Africa.
	</event>
	
	<event start="Nov 14 2011" title="Yemaso BJJ">
	Team Sacramento Judo relocates it's Sacramento dojo to the Yemaso Brazilian Jiu Jitsu facility.
	</event>


	
</data>